cityfurniture.com 2019-09-22

# City Furniture | Customer Care | Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Statement explains how we at City Furniture, Inc. protect the privacy of information about our customers and how we manage your information carefully when providing products and services.

#### How We Gather and Use Information About You

There may be times (such as when you purchase or order a product, browse our catalogues or register to received product information) when we ask you to provide certain information about yourself, such as your name, address, telephone number, email address and the like. We may also maintain certain general information about your purchase history with us. The information you provide to us is strictly your choice. However, if you decide not to provide information about yourself to us it may preclude you from purchasing products or accessing certain services.

When you use our online site to shop, purchase, or simply browse, we may collect technical information about your browser, contact information, customer feedback and purchasing history. We use this information to customize your on-line experience with us, enhance your shopping experience, respond to your inquiries about products and delivery and improve our site to make it a more satisfying experience for our customers.

#### Cookies

Cookies are a tool used throughout the internet to describe bits of information that most web sites create when you visit their sites and then store on your computer. Cookies are unique to the computer being used and can only be read by the web site who placed it on your computer. It only stores information specific to the computer, not the user’s personal information. They cannot be used to extract information from your computer, only to simply identify the computer.

City Furniture, Inc. may use Cookies to help facilitate your online experience, assist you with navigating the content of our site, help to personalize your site experience with us, to evaluate our web site and advertising or promotions, and for our Customer Protection. Although we do not collect any personally identifiable information through the use of cookies, we may contract with other companies to assist us in setting cookies for the purposes described above. We are committed to not sharing the information we garner with other companies.

To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online, or in our stores. We may also combine that information with publicly available information and information we receive from or cross-reference with our Select Partners and others. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize the shopping experience of you and others with us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes.

We may contract with companies or persons to provide certain services including credit card processing, shipping, data management, promotional services, etc. 

#### Using Information About You

We use the contact information you provide for internal purposes, such as confirming and tracking your order, subscription or registration, 

analyzing preferences, trends and statistics, informing you of our new products, services and offers, and providing you with information from and about City Furniture. From time to time we may establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy policies are consistent with ours. These are known as our Select Partners. In such cases we might rent, exchange, share and/or cross-reference information, including contact information about you that will enable such persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you.

To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online, or in our stores with publicly available information or information we receive by cross-referencing with our Partners. This combined information may be used to contact you with promotional or sales information. 

We also may contract with companies or persons to provide certain services including credit card processing. We call them our Service Providers. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. We also ask our Service Providers to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours.

Although unlikely, in certain instances we may disclose your contact information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to City Furniture, Inc or to others. We may also disclose your contact information when we believe the law or legal process requires it.

#### Updating or Editing Information of Customers

We want to communicate with you only if you want us to. If you prefer to not receive promotional mailings or direct marketing, or you would like to opt out of receiving information, please let us know. 

#### Reporting Suspicious or Fraudulent Activity Involving Your City Furniture Account

If you receive a suspicious email message that appears to be coming from City Furniture, Inc. or discover a potentially phony City Furniture site, please let us know immediately by emailing customerservice@cityfurniture.com or by contacting our [corporate offices](https://www.cityfurniture.com/help-center "contact us") directly. We take these incidents seriously and will conduct an investigation of each incident with the help of law enforcement.

#### Protecting Children's Privacy

We respect the privacy of your children, and we comply with the practices established under the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. We do not knowingly collect or retain personally identifiable information from consumers under the age of thirteen. For more information about the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act please refer to the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) website.

Children under the age of 13 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any contact information to anyone online. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their children’s online activities and use parental control or other web filtering technology to supervise children’s access to the web.
